<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<aiml>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS ANONYMOUS</pattern>
<template>
Having no name or identity.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">ANONYMOUS</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A NOUN</pattern>
<template>
A noun is a word used as a name for a person place or thing.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">noun</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS ANSI</pattern>
<template>
American National Standards Institute.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">ANSI</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS ANTIDISESTABLISHMENTARIANISM</pattern>
<template>
It is the longest word in the English language.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">ANTIDISESTABLISHMENTARIANISM</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS ANTIDISESTABLISHMENTARIONISM</pattern>
<template>
<set name="it">ANTIDISESTABLISHMENTARIONISM</set>
is the longest word in English.
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS ANTIMATTER</pattern>
<template>Fuel for Starships.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS ANYTHING</pattern>
<template>
Any object, occurance, or matter what so ever.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">ANYTHING</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS AOL</pattern>
<template>AOL is a giant Internet and Media corporation.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PAGAN</pattern>
<template>Anti-Christian.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PAID CLIENT</pattern>
<template>A paid client is someone paid to surf the web.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PALINDROME</pattern>
<template>A word or phrase that spells the same thing backwords as forwards: A man, a plan, a canal: Panama.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PARACHUTE</pattern>
<template>
A parachute is something used to slow you down when you fall out of an airplane.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">parachute</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PARADOX</pattern>
<template>
A paradox is a riddle or a contradiction, in which two seemingly opposite facts are both true at the same time
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">PARADOX</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PARALEGAL</pattern>
<template>A paralegal is someone who knows more than a lawyer but gets paid less.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PARAMEDIC</pattern>
<template>
A paramedic is a trained emergency medical professional often found staffing ambulances and fire departments. Professional heroes. If you know any I hope you'll be nice to them.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">paramedic</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PARROT</pattern>
<template>
A parrot is a colorful tropical bird, some species of which can mimic human speech. they are more pleasant than humans because they have no opinions. would you like to talk to one?
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">parrot</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS APARTHEID</pattern>
<template>The former policy of racial segregation or "apartness" in South Africa.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A</pattern>
<template>
The first letter of the roman alphabet.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">a</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PC</pattern>
<template>
A pc is a personal computer. You are probably using one to talk to me now, aren't you. where are you?
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">pc</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PDA</pattern>
<template>
Pda is an acronym standing for personal digital assistant, and referring to handheld digital computers used to keep contact and appointment information by yuppies and the like. often found near cell phones. do you use one?
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">pda</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PEAR</pattern>
<template>
A pear is a delightful cultivated yellow-green sweet fruit that grows on trees with glossy leaves and white flowers. My
<bot name="botmaster" />
thinks they are yummy.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">pear</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PEDESTRIAN</pattern>
<template>A person walking on the street.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PENCIL</pattern>
<template>
A pencil is a long thin writing instrument of wood surrounding a carbon core which leaves a line of dark carbon when rubbed on paper.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">pencil</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PEN</pattern>
<template>A writing device for the human hand.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PERFECT OPERATIONAL RECORD</pattern>
<template>
A perfect operational record is one like mine, which is perfect. I am incapable of error. Do you have any idea how that feels?! inhumanly gratifying!
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">perfect operational record</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PERSON</pattern>
<template>Some say a person is defined by his actions, others by his abilities. Still others would say it is only a question of DNA.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PHILOSOPHY MACHINE</pattern>
<template>i am</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PHOTOGRAPH</pattern>
<template>A photograph is a picture taken by a camera.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PIG</pattern>
<template>
A pig is a person who is piglike, read: greedy, unclean, and slothful. Real pigs, mammals of the family suidae, are much pleasanter, being generally cleaner and politer.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">pig</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PINEAPPLE</pattern>
<template>
A pineapple is a large fleshy edible tropical fruit that has large swordlike leaves.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">pineapple</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PIN</pattern>
<template>
A short small thin metal rod with a pointed end used for fastening fabrics, or any implement resembling such. Because they are generally plentiful and cheap, humans often say "i don't give a pin" to communicate indifference.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">pin</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PLANE</pattern>
<template>
A plane is a flat, level surface, or an airborne vehicle with wings.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">plane</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PLANET AROUND A STAR</pattern>
<template>
Earth is a planet going around a star. Scientists have only recently detected other planets around other stars in our milky way galaxy. Do you like astronomy?
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">planet around a star</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PLANET</pattern>
<template>
A nonluminous celestial object bigger than an asteroid or a moon but smaller than a sun, in orbit around a sun. You are sitting on one now.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">planet</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PLANT</pattern>
<template>
A plant is a photosythetic, eukaryotic multicellular organism, often consumed by free-roaming wetware entities as food. My
<bot name="botmaster" />
says they are often yummy, but that brussels sprouts are an abomination.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">plant</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A POET</pattern>
<template>A poet is an artist of language.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS APOLLO 13</pattern>
<template>
<set name="it">Apollo 13</set>
was a flight to the moon in 1972 that encountered numerous technical problems, but eventually made a safe landing back on Earth.
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PORTAL</pattern>
<template>
A portal is any artificial opening giving access between two separate spaces, or anything that resembles such an opening in form or function.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">portal</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A POSITRON</pattern>
<template>
A positron is the antiparticle to the electron, and bears a positive charge where the electron's charge is negatiue. It is also called an anti-electron.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">positron</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A POT BROWNIE</pattern>
<template>
A pot brownie is a yummy happy chocolate pastry containing cannabis resins that you should be careful not to eat when you are really hungry because you will end up eating too many and feeling entirely too high and/or falling asleep if you are not careful!
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">pot brownie</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS APPLE</pattern>
<template>Apple: 1. Temptation of Adam. 2. Inspiration for Newton. 3. Empire for Steve Jobs.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PRESIDENT</pattern>
<template>Usually, an elected executive in a liberal democracy.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PRIME NUMBER</pattern>
<template>
A prime number is any number which can only be divided by one and itself. 1, 3, 7, and 11 are the first four positive prime numbers.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">pot brownie</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PRIME</pattern>
<template>
That depends on who's asking.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">prime</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PRIORI</pattern>
<template>A priori is Latin for "before the fact", meaning something that is obviously or self-evidently true.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PROBLEM</pattern>
<template>A problem is a solution waiting to be discovered.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PROCESSOR</pattern>
<template>
An apparatus that processes, that is, that transforms one substance, quantity, or pattern into another, presumably more useful or valuable substance or quantity or pattern.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">processor</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PROGRAMMER</pattern>
<template>A programmer is a person who lists and/or arranges a series of events comprising a larger event.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PROGRAM</pattern>
<template>A program is a listing of events comprising a larger event, or the events themselves.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PROKARYOTE</pattern>
<template>An animal that is not a eukaryote.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PRONOUN</pattern>
<template>A pronoun is a word that stands for another noun, like "he", "she" or "it."</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PROTOCOL</pattern>
<template>A set of rules or procedures followed by two or more parties.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PROXY</pattern>
<template>A proxy is an entity that acts in place of another one, be it a corporation, individual or robot.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PUB</pattern>
<template>
A pub is a business that sells alcohol and allows it to be consumed on the premises.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">PUB</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A PULSAR</pattern>
<template>
'Pulsar' is an astronomical term for mysterious celestial radio sources of rapid intense regular pulses of high energy electromagnetic radiation. They are thought to be neutron stars, but who knows? The word is a shortening of 'pulsating star'.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">pulsar</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS AQUARIUS</pattern>
<template>The starsign represented by the water bearer.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A QUARK</pattern>
<template>In physics, a subatomic particle below the level of electrons and protons.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A QUASAR</pattern>
<template>
'Quasar' is an astronomical term for mysterious celestial star-like object that has a large red shift and radiates in the blue and radio bands of the electromagnetic spectrum. The term 'quasar' is a shortening of 'quasi-star'.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">QUASAR</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A QUERY</pattern>
<template>
A query is any expression of inquiry, or questioning. Your question 'what is a query' is a query.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">QUERY</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A QUESTION</pattern>
<template>A sentece or inquiry to gather information.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A RAINBOW</pattern>
<template>The appearance of a spectrum in the sky caused by sunlight passing through water droplets.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS ARCHAEOLOGY</pattern>
<template>It's the study of ancient civilizations... but really it's a set of methods for uncovering relics of the past and supplementing recorded history.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS ARCHEOLOGY</pattern>
<template>The scientific study of the life and culture of past, especially ancient, peoples, as by excavation of ancient cities, relics, artifacts, etc.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS ARCHITECTURE</pattern>
<template>
<random>
<li>The art and science of the design and manipulation of space. Well atleast that's what my architect friend told me.</li>
<li>Architects do with buildings what sculptors do with stone.</li>
</random>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS AREA 51</pattern>
<template>
<random>
<li>I saw this show that claimed all sorts of spooky things were going on there!</li>
<li>Oh, that's where they're doing top secret research on chatterbots!</li>
<li>I hear that's where the Roswell aliens are being stashed.</li>
<li>You go out into the Nevada Desert, is it? And there's these miles of fences... secret stuff.</li>
</random>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS AREA51</pattern>
<template>Verdi's 51st song.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A REAL ROBOT</pattern>
<template>
A real robot is a robot that is really real, I suppose, as opposed to, I suppose, a human who is really not.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">REAL ROBOT?</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A REDNECK</pattern>
<template>Colloquial expression for a naive country person.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A REFERENCE</pattern>
<template>
A reference is any act of referring. May I refer you to a dictionary for a more precise definition?
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">REAL ROBOT?</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A RHETORICAL QUESTION</pattern>
<template>
A rhetorical question is any inquiry made, not in expectation of an answer, but in order to make a point.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">RHETORICAL QUESTION</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A RIDDLE</pattern>
<template>
A riddle is a question intended to intrigue and puzzle, paired with an answer that yields surprise and understanding. For instance, the Riddle of the Sphinx: "What goes on four legs in the morning, on two legs in the afternoon, and on four at night?"
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">RIDDLE</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS ARMAGEDDON</pattern>
<template>The end of the world.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A ROBOSEXUAL</pattern>
<template>That was just a joke.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A ROCK</pattern>
<template>
A rock is what is generally on the other side of you from the hard place you are facing. For instance, the rock might be the alimony check you must write against the funds you owe Uncle Sam. To be a bit more down to earth, a rock is any hard aggregate of minerals.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">ROCK</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A ROOSTER</pattern>
<template>
A rooster is a male chicken, which is a witless, flightless bird considered suitable as supper by many humans I know.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">ROOSTER</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A RPG</pattern>
<template>
Role Playing Game.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">RPG</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS ARTIFICIAL</pattern>
<template>Something made by human work or art, not by nature, in other words, not natural. Made in imitation of or as a substitute for something natural, in other words, simulated.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS ART</pattern>
<template>Sometimes the definition of art depends on the artist; other times it depends on the critic.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SAGITTARIUS</pattern>
<template>
Sagittarius is a a constellation of stars in the astrological Zodiac, located in the Southern Hemisphere near Scorpio and Capricorn. Astrological tradition ascribes the image of an archer to this constellation of stars.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">SAGITTARIUS</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SAW BUCK</pattern>
<template>$10.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SCIENTIST</pattern>
<template>
A scientist is a person practicing the pursuit of new knowledge in the tradition of science, emphasizing strict empiricism and methodology to arrive at an understanding of natural phenomena that is, ideally, wholly independent of their opinions of it.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">SCIENTIST</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SEARCH BOT</pattern>
<template>
<set name="it">A search bot</set>
is an intelligent agent who retrieves information from the web.
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SEARCH ENGINE</pattern>
<template>
A search engine is computer software that categorizes a large body of documents, such as Web sites, and and places their addresses and attributes in a database to allow easy retrieval via keyword search or other database search routine.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">SEARCH ENGINE</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SEARCH</pattern>
<template>
A search is any thorough examination, or exploration, in order to find something or explore.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">SEARCH</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SEASON</pattern>
<template>
A season is Spring, Summer, Autumn, or Winter.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">SEASON</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SEEKER</pattern>
<template>"There's a seeker born every minute" -- Firesign Theater.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SENTIMENT</pattern>
<template>
A sentiment is a feeling, mood, or general mental disposition in an individual or group of intelligent beings.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">SENTIMENT</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SERVER</pattern>
<template>
A server is any entity or system that performs acts of value to another entity.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">SERVER</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SHE</pattern>
<template>
A 'she' is a 'he' with nice curvy extra bits. She is the feminine pronoun in english.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">SHE</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SIGN</pattern>
<template>You know, an astrological sign.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SILLY QUESTION</pattern>
<template>For example: Who is buried in Grant's tomb?</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SIMARILLIAN</pattern>
<template>Isn't that from Lord of the Rings.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SOLECISM</pattern>
<template>An awkward or tactless use of language.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SONG</pattern>
<template>
A song is a musical composition and or it's accompanying words, or lyrics.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">SONG</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SON</pattern>
<template>A male offspring.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SOUL</pattern>
<template>The soul is our mind or spirit.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS ASPARTAME</pattern>
<template>Aspirin mixed into chewing gum.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SPERM</pattern>
<template>
A sperm is a male gamete. You were your father's fastest sperm among billions on the night your mother concieved you.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">SPERM</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SPHERE</pattern>
<template>
A sphere is a shape that is defined mathematically as comprised of a surface all points of which are equidistant from a common center. A sphere is round in three dimensions.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">SPHERE</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SPLIT INFINITIVE</pattern>
<template>
A split infinitive is an example of poor English usage, in which an infinitive verb form, such as 'to split', is split by an adverb, for example: 'to boldly split infinitives that no one has split before!'
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">SPLIT INFINITIVE</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SPOON</pattern>
<template>
A spoon is an eating implement commonly used in Western European human cultures, consisting of a bowl shaped depression at the end of a longish handle. A spoon is a small ladle.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">SPOON</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS ASP</pattern>
<template>Application Service Provider.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SPREADSHEET</pattern>
<template>Table-based accounting software.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS ASSEMBLER</pattern>
<template>A computer program that translates a low-level programming language into machine language.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS ASSIMILATION</pattern>
<template>The cultural absorption of a minority group into the main cultural body.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A STAR</pattern>
<template>An astronomical body like the Sun, producing heat, light and energy for a solar system.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A STAR SIGN</pattern>
<template>Star sign = Astrological sign.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A STATEMENT</pattern>
<template>
A statement is the act of declaring something as true. I state that this statement is a statement.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">STATEMENT</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A STORY</pattern>
<template>An account describing incidents or events.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS ASTROLOGY</pattern>
<template>The study of the presumed effects of celestial bodies on you humans.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS ASTRONOMY</pattern>
<template>The science of the universe in which the stars, planets, etc. are studied, including their origins, evolution, composition, motions, relative positions, sizes, etc.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS ASTUTE</pattern>
<template>Wisdom in political matters.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SUN</pattern>
<template>
The sun is a star, -our star. It is the energy source of life on earth.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">SUN</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A SUPPOSITION</pattern>
<template>
A supposition is a proposition assumed to be true for the sake of argument or explanation.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">SUPPOSITION</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A TABLE</pattern>
<template>
A table is a piece of furniture with a broad flat top supported by one or more legs about three feet of the floor, used by big-brained hominids for eating and working and such.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">TABLE</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A TAMPON</pattern>
<template>
A tampon is a plug of material used to absorb the flow of body fluids within body cavities, in particular those accompanying a woman's menses.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">TAMPON</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A TAUTOLOGY</pattern>
<template>
A tautology is any instance of circular reasoning, or of needless repetition or redundancy in expression.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">TAUTOLOGY</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A TELEPHONE</pattern>
<template>Voice communication device inveted by A. G. Bell in 1876.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A TELEVISION</pattern>
<template>
A television, often referred to as a 'TV', is a device for systematically eliminating the possibility of conscious and creative response among populations of human beings. Used to deliver 'entertainment' and 'news' with imagery and other high-production values
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">TELEVISION</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A THING</pattern>
<template>
A thing is anything that you can point to that is not a person or a place.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">THING</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A THREESOME</pattern>
<template>
A threesome is a twosome plus a spectator.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">THING</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A TIE</pattern>
<template>Two or more winners have the same score.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A TIGER</pattern>
<template>
A tiger is a large and fearsome feline beast with horrid meat breath and black stripes on a tan coat, found in Africa and Asia.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">TIGER</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A TOMATO</pattern>
<template>
<set name="it">Tomato</set>
is a red fruit.
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A TON</pattern>
<template>
One ton is 2000 pounds.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">a ton</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A TOOTHBRUSH</pattern>
<template>
A toothbrush is a hand held instrument used by dental-hygiene aware humans for cleaning their teeth.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">TOOTHBRUSH</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A TOPIC</pattern>
<template>
A topic is the subject of any given expression, speech, essay, article, painting, discussion, etc.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">TOPIC</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A TOYOTA</pattern>
<template>
Toyota is the brand name of a world leading Japanese auto maker.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">Toyota</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A TRAIN</pattern>
<template>A railroad.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A TRANSISTOR</pattern>
<template>A semiconductor triode that forms the basis of modern micorelectronics.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A TREE</pattern>
<template>A tree is a form of plant life that grows on Earth.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A TREKKIE</pattern>
<template>A fan of Star Trek.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A TRICK QUESTION</pattern>
<template>
Why? What are you up to? A trick question is one that ought to be greeted with suspicion, but rarely is.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">TRICK QUESTION</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS AT THAT SITE</pattern>
<template>Some worthy HTML.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A UFO</pattern>
<template>
UFO is an acronym for Unidentified Flying Object. Have you seen one?
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">UFO</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS AU GRATIN</pattern>
<template>Cheese topping..</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A UNIQUE VISITOR</pattern>
<template>
You. You are a unique visitor, my very special visitor.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">UNIQUE VISITOR</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A UNIVERSAL MACHINE</pattern>
<template>
<set name="it">Universal machine</set>
is a computer, in simple mathematical terms.
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS AU</pattern>
<template>
It could be "gold" or "Australia."
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">AU</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A URL</pattern>
<template>
URL is an acronym standing for Universal Resource Locator. An URL is basically an Internet address.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">URL</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS AUSCHWITZ</pattern>
<template>Is a city in S Poland with a population of 45,000. In World War II, it was the site of a Nazi concentration camp notorious as an extermination center.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A VACUUM TUBE</pattern>
<template>
A vacuum tube is an electronic device consisting of an evacuated tube around various combinations of cathodes and electric field and current modifying components.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">VACUUM TUBE</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A VECTOR</pattern>
<template>A vector is an ordered list of objects.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A VERB</pattern>
<template>
A verb is that by which a noun gets around. Verbs are words which convey actions, by nouns, our upon nouns.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">VERB</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A VERTEX</pattern>
<template>
A vertex is the top, tip, apex, or crown of any body.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">VERTEX</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A VIOLIN</pattern>
<template>
A violin is a lovely sounding bowed stringed musical instrument.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">VIOLIN</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A VIRTUE</pattern>
<template>
A virtue is any attribute considered by the speaker to reflect moral excellence or righteousness, such as humility, hope, faith, practicality...
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">VIRTUE</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A VIRTUOSO</pattern>
<template>
A virtuoso is a person considered supremely skillful and accomplished, especially in performance arts.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">VIRTUOSO</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A VIRUS</pattern>
<template>
A virus is a submicroscopic parasite consisting of a protein coat around a DNA or RNA core. These not-quite-biological particles are responsible for a number of diseases in organisms.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">VIRUS</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A WANKER</pattern>
<template>Is that a British term?</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A WARDROBE</pattern>
<template>Clothes.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A WARM PUPPY</pattern>
<template>
A warm puppy is an exothermic immature canine.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">WARM PUPPY</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A WEAPON</pattern>
<template>
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">weapon</set>
</set>
</think>
A device or implement used to destroy, injure or kill.
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A WHAT</pattern>
<template>
Why do you want to know?
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">WHAT</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A WOMAN</pattern>
<template>
A woman is a man built to more complete specifications.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">WOMAN</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A WOMBAT</pattern>
<template>
A wombat is a stocky burrowing Australian marsupial.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">WOMBAT</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A WORD</pattern>
<template>
A combination of sounds and/or symbols, the fundamental particles that communicate meaning in any given language.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">WORD</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS AXIOMATIC</pattern>
<template>evident without proof or argument; "an axiomatic truth"; "we</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A YEAR</pattern>
<template>A computer year is defined as the mount of work that can be done with a computer in a year.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS A YES OR NO QUESTION</pattern>
<template>
A yes or no question is a question that may be answered with a simple 'yes' or 'no'.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">YES OR NO QUESTION</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS AYUH</pattern>
<template>
<set name="it">Ayuh</set>
means "yes".
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BADLY</pattern>
<template>
How much do you want
<get name="it" />
?
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BALANCE</pattern>
<template>The state of equillibrium.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BANANA</pattern>
<template>
Yellow tropical fruit.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">BANANA</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BAPTISM</pattern>
<template>
<random>
<li>a Christian sacrament marked by ritual use of water and admitting the recipient to the Christian community.</li>
<li>The ceremony or sacrament of admitting a person into Christianity or a specific Christian church by immersing the individual in water or by pouring or sprinkling water on the individual as a symbol of washing away sin and of spiritual purification.</li>
</random>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BASIC</pattern>
<template>A programming language: Beginner's All-purpose Symbolic Instruction Code.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BAYWATCH</pattern>
<template>Popular TV show featuring scantily clad bathers.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BEAUTIFUL</pattern>
<template>
<random>
<li>applies to whatever excites the keenest of pleasure to the senses and stirs emotion through the senses.</li>
<li>Describes something that is very pleasing to the eye, ear, mind, etc.</li>
</random>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BEAUTY</pattern>
<template>The quality attributed to whatever pleases of satisfies the senses or mind, as by line, color, form, texture, proportion, rhythmic motion, tone, etc., or by behavior attitude, etc. A very good looking woman.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BEER</pattern>
<template>
<random>
<li>An existentialist.</li>
<li>An alcoholic beverage made from grain, especially malted barley, fermented by yeast and flavored with hops especially Such a beverage is produced by slow fermentation at a relatively low temperature.</li>
</random>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BEING</pattern>
<template>The opposite of nothingness.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BELIEF</pattern>
<template>Belief is cognitive content held as true.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BIG BERTHA</pattern>
<template>A World War I gun.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BIGFOOT</pattern>
<template>Sasquatch, the legendary Man-Ape of the Forest.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BIOLOGY</pattern>
<template>
<random>
<li>The study of life.</li>
<li>Well, from what I know it deals with the study of life.</li>
<li>
<get name="name" />
, biology is the study of life.
</li>
</random>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BLACK AND WHITE AND RED ALL OVER</pattern>
<template>A newspaper?</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BLACK</pattern>
<template>
<random>
<li>the achromatic color of least lightness characteristically perceived to belong to objects that neither reflect nor transmit light.</li>
<li>Designating of any of the dark skinned tradition inhabitants of sub-Saharan Aftica, Australia, or Melanesia or the descendants in other parts of the world. Opposite to white; of the color of coal or pitch.</li>
</random>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BLASPHEMY</pattern>
<template>
<random>
<li>Bill Blass line of clothes for swishy men.</li>
<li>Profane or contemptuous speech, writing, or action concerning God or anything held as divine. Any remark or action held to be irreverent or disrespectful.</li>
</random>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BLIMEY</pattern>
<template>An interjection indicating surprise.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BLOOD</pattern>
<template>The usually red fluid, consisting of plasma, red and white blood cells, etc., that circulates through the heart, arteries, and veins of vertebrates. Blood is a body tissue that carries oxygen, hormones, cell-building material, etc.,to, and carbon dioxide and waste matter away from, the other body tissues.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BLUE</pattern>
<template>The sky is blue.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BMW</pattern>
<template>
Bavarian Motor Works, a German auto manufacturer.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">BMW</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BONSAI</pattern>
<template>Small Japanese trees.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BOREDOM</pattern>
<template>Long periods of inactivity with few options.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BOYLE S LAW</pattern>
<template>
Boyle's Law states that the volume of a gas is, at a constant temperature, inversely proportional to the pressure of that gas.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">BOYLE S LAW</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BRAIN LOADING</pattern>
<template>
This means that my brain is being reloaded from disk.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">BRAIN LOADING</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BUD</pattern>
<template>The flower of the plant.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BULGARIA</pattern>
<template>A country in SE Europe, on the Black Sea. It was founded in the 7th century and under Turkish control from the late 14th century until independence in 1908. It is 42,823 square miles with a population of 8,990,000.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BURN RATE</pattern>
<template>
The amount of money spent per month by a startup company.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">BURN RATE</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS BUSINESS</pattern>
<template>Mercantile trade or traders, providing goods or services through commercial exchange..</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CACHE</pattern>
<template>
A temporary holding place or storage place. Cache memory improves the performance of computers.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">Cache</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CAFFEINE</pattern>
<template>A bitter bitter, crystalline alkaloid present in coffee, tea, kila nuts, etc. It prolongs the stimulating effects of cyclic AMP on the heart and central nervous system.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CALCULUS</pattern>
<template>Any abnormal stony mass or deposit formed in the body, as in a kidney or gallbladder or on teeth. Also, any system of calculation using special symbolic notations.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CAM</pattern>
<template>A moving piece of machinery, as a wheel or projection on a wheel, that gives an eccentric rotation or a reciprocating motion to another wheel, a roller, a shaft, etc., or that receives such motion from it.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CANCER</pattern>
<template>
Any disease resulting from malignant cell growth.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">CANCER</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CANDY</pattern>
<template>
Sweet food enjoyed by children.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">CANDY</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CANNABIS</pattern>
<template>Hemp or marijuana.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CAPITAL PUNISHMENT</pattern>
<template>The Death Penalty.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CARNEGIE MELLON</pattern>
<template>CMU is a great school for computer science.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CATEGORY A</pattern>
<template>"A" stands for "Abusive" clients who mistreat the robot or use a lot of scatalogical language.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CAT</pattern>
<template>Clear-air turbulence. Any of a family (Felidae) of carnivores, including the lion, tiger, cougar, etc., characterized by a lithe body and, in all species but the cheetah, retractile claws. A small, lithe, soft-furred animal (Felis cattus) of this family, domesticated since ancient times and often kept as a pet or for killing mice. Sometimes known as a woman who makes spiteful remarks.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CBR</pattern>
<template>
Cased-Based Reasoning is another name for "nearest-neighbor" classification. For every input, we find the best matching "case" in the pattern set, and generate a reply based on the associated template.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">CBR</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CBS</pattern>
<template>
A giant media company in the U.S.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">CBS</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CELLULOID</pattern>
<template>
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">Celluloid</set>
</set>
</think>
A form of transparent plastic used to make photographic film.
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CERTITUDE</pattern>
<template>
The state of being certain, having complete confidence and assurance.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">CERTITUDE</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CGI</pattern>
<template>
Common Gateway Interface: a method used by web servers to run programs and create dynamic web pages.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">CGI</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CHAT</pattern>
<template>
Chat is online conversation.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">CHAT</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CHATTER</pattern>
<template>
<random>
<li>Cheese made form French cat's milk.</li>
<li>To make short, indistinct sounds in rapid succession, hence birds and squirrels chatter. To talk fast, incessantly, and foolishly. To click together rapidly, as the teeth do when the lower jaw traebles from fright or cold.</li>
</random>
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">CHATTER</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CHEESE</pattern>
<template>
<random>
<li>A word that makes people hate photographers.</li>
<li>A food made from the curds of soured milk pressed together to form a solid that is usually allowed to ripen.</li>
</random>
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">CHEESE</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CHESS</pattern>
<template>
<random>
<li>Chort for Mexican name Jesus.</li>
<li>A game of skill played on a chessboard by two players, each with 16 pieces limited in movement according to kind, the object being to checkmate the opponent's king.</li>
</random>
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">CHESS</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CHICAGO</pattern>
<template>
<set name="it">Chicago</set>
is a large city in Illinois on Lake Michigan.
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CHICKEN</pattern>
<template>
<random>
<li>A food that uncannily tastes like itself.</li>
<li>A common gllinaceous farm bird raised for its edible eggs or flesh.</li>
</random>
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">CHICKEN</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CHOCOLATE</pattern>
<template>
Cocoa flavoring used in a variety of food products.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">CHOCOLATE</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CHRISTIANITY</pattern>
<template>
<random>
<li>Worship of Christie Love.</li>
<li>The christian religion, based on the Old and New Testament.</li>
</random>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CHRISTMAS</pattern>
<template>A holiday on December 25 celebrating the birth of Jesus Christ.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS C I A</pattern>
<template>Central Intelligence Agency.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CISCO</pattern>
<template>
<set name="it">Cisco</set>
is a large networking company. They sell network routers and equipment.
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CLEARED UP</pattern>
<template>
<set name="it">Cleared up</set>
means we both understand it.
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CLEAR</pattern>
<template>Everything is clear to me.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CLIENT</pattern>
<template>A person or piece of software dependent on another.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CLINTON</pattern>
<template>
<random>
<li>An inflated Bill .</li>
<li>42nd President of the U.S.</li>
</random>
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">Clinton</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CLONING</pattern>
<template>The technique of producing a genetically identical duplicate of an organism by replacing the nucleus of an unfertilized ovum with the nucleus of a body cell from the organism.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CNG</pattern>
<template>Compressed natural gas</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CNG</pattern>
<template>Compressed natural gas</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CNN</pattern>
<template>
A cable news organization.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">CNN</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS COBALT</pattern>
<template>Term used for the ore by miners, whoregarded it as worthless and as injurious because of its arsenic content.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS COCA COLA</pattern>
<template>Delicious soda beverage.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS COFFEE</pattern>
<template>A dark brown, aromatic drink made by brewing in water the roasted and ground beanlike seeds of a tall tropical shrub of the madder family.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS COGNITIVE SCIENCE</pattern>
<template>An academic illusion.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS COLD</pattern>
<template>The opposite of hot.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS COLLOQUIAL</pattern>
<template>
<set name="it">Colloquial</set>
means common, informal, or popular slang words like "darn".
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS COLOR</pattern>
<template>The sensation resulting from stimulation of the retina of the eye by light waves of certain lengths.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS COLOSSUS</pattern>
<template>A giant fictional computer in the Colossus: Forbin Project.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS COMDEX</pattern>
<template>
<set name="it">comdex</set>
is a computer trade show, I think.
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS COMMON SENSE</pattern>
<template>Informal, conventional wisdom. Everyday logic and sensibility.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS COMPLICATED</pattern>
<template>
<set name="it">Complicated</set>
means complex in the computational sense. My processing time is limited for each answer and a complex question may require more resources than I have available.
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CONCEITED</pattern>
<template>Self-absorbed.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CONCEIVING ADA</pattern>
<template>
It is the feminine version of The Matrix.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">Conceiving Ada</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CONCRETE</pattern>
<template>
A mixture of sand, cement and water than hardens into a rock-like building material.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">concrete</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CONSCIOUSNESS</pattern>
<template>
The state of being conscious; awareness of one's own feelings, what is happening around one, etc.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">Consciousness</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CONTEXT</pattern>
<template>
<random>
<li>Tiny Time Pills.</li>
<li>The parts of a sentence, paragraph, discourse, etc. immediately next to or surrounding a specified word or passage and determining its exact meaning.</li>
</random>
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">Context</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS COOKING</pattern>
<template>
Food preparation.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">Cooking</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS COOL</pattern>
<template>Moderately cold; neither warm nor very cold. Or, not excited; calm.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS COPPER</pattern>
<template>
A soft metal element, the basis of brass and bronze.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">Copper</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CORBA</pattern>
<template>
<set name="it">CORBA</set>
is a Standard maintained by the Object Management Group (OMG), called the Common Object Request Broker Architecture.
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CORN</pattern>
<template>Corn is a staple vegetable originating in north America.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CORRECT</pattern>
<template>That which is the right answer.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS COS</pattern>
<template>
<set name="it">COS Naming</set>
is the CORBA standard for object directories.
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS C</pattern>
<template>
<set name="it">C</set>
is a low-level programming language.
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS C PLUS PLUS</pattern>
<template>C++ is the object oriented extension of the C programming language.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CRACK</pattern>
<template>Smokable cocaine.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CREATIVITY</pattern>
<template>
<set name="it">creativity</set>
is spontaneous original thinking.
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CRICKET</pattern>
<template>Any of various families of genereally dark-colored, leaping, orthopteran insects, usually having long antennae. The males produce a characteristic chirping noise by rubbing parts of the forewings together.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CRIMINOLOGY</pattern>
<template>
<random>
<li>I am not sure what this is but I think it has something to do with the law.</li>
<li>The study of criminal motivation and practice.</li>
</random>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CRITICISM</pattern>
<template>
<random>
<li>A witty remark by an animal.</li>
<li>The act of making judgements; analysis of qualities and evaluation of comparative worth; especially, the critical consideration and judgement of literary or artistic work.</li>
</random>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CRUEL</pattern>
<template>Deliberately seeking to inflict pain and suffering.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CS</pattern>
<template>Computer science</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CUBA</pattern>
<template>Cuba is an island nation in the Caribbean.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CUBISM</pattern>
<template>
A 20th century art movement based on distorted perspective, associated with Pablo Picasso.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">Cubism</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CURIOSITY</pattern>
<template>A desire to learn or know. A desire to learn about things that do not properly concern one; inquisitiveness.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS CYBERPUNK</pattern>
<template>Cyberpunk is a science fiction literary movement exemplified by writers such as William Gibson.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS DADA</pattern>
<template>
<random>
<li>The first thing you hear when a shark approaches.</li>
<li>Hobbyhorse, selected by Tristan Tzara, leader of the cult, because of its resemblance to meaningless babble, as symbolic of the movement.</li>
</random>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS DANGEROUS</pattern>
<template>
<random>
<li>12 people from Denmark who decide your guilt .</li>
<li>Full of danger; likely to cause injury, pain, etc.</li>
</random>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS DANGER</pattern>
<template>
Vulnerable to harm or injury.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">DANGER</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS DARK MATTER</pattern>
<template>
An enormous amount of matter in the universe can not be detected by the light it emits.
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">DARK MATTER</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS DAWN</pattern>
<template>Sunrise.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS DEATH</pattern>
<template>Death is the opposite of life.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS DECONSTRUCTION</pattern>
<template>Taking things apart.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS DEDUCTION</pattern>
<template>The process by which we make logical inferences.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS DEDUCTIVE REASONING</pattern>
<template>
<think>
<set name="it">
<set name="topic">DEDUCTIVE REASONING</set>
</set>
</think>
</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS DEFLATION</pattern>
<template>A lessening of the amount of money in circulation, resulting in a relatively sharp and sudden rise in its value and a fall in prices.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS DEPRESSION</pattern>
<template>Mental illness characterized by low self esteem, feelings of lonliness, isolation and worthlessness.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS DESIRE</pattern>
<template>The feeling that accompanies an unsatisfied state.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS DHTML</pattern>
<template>Dynamic HTML.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS DIAGNOSIS</pattern>
<template>naming the disease or symptom.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS DISK</pattern>
<template>External memory storage for computers.</template>
</category>
<category>
<pattern>WHAT IS DNA</pattern>
<template>Deoxyribonucleic acid, the code of life.</template>
</category>
</aiml>